worldsbestpubcrawls.com 2011-05-03

# Thirsty Swagman

Thirsty Swagman respects your privacy.  We do not rent or sell any of the details that you provide to us in good faith.  We do our utmost to ensure the privacy and security of the information you supply  to us.  We do not buy or rent information from any third parties.  If you receive information from Swagman Tours, it is because you have requested it - or a friend / colleague has requested it on your behalf.  At any time you can be removed from any or all of our databases and receive no more information from us.  Please send an email to [info@thirstyswagman.com](mailto:info@thirstyswagman.com) to be removed.

**What information is collected by Thirsty Swagman?**  
Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email address or telephone numbers) for various purposes on this site, or directly to our offices.  These purposes include registering to receive e-mail newsletters, requesting further information about our trips, or simply asking a question.  Thirsty Swagman does not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us.  This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself.

**How is information used?**  
When you supply information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (to provide the service or information you have requested).  We do not divulge any information we gather from you to any third party without your prior consent.  If making a booking with us, additional information will be required for operational reasons.

**Security**  
Personally identifiable information is stored on servers that are not publicly accessible.  Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by Thirsty Swagman employees on a "need to know" basis.

**Choice / opt-out**  
If you have registered to receive communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. Specific details of unsubscription actions are contained in each communication piece, or, you can send an e-mail to [info@thirstyswagman.com](mailto:info@thirstyswagman.com)

**Correct / update**  
If you would like to verify the data we have received from you or to make corrections to it, you may contact us directly.

**What anonymous information is collected on this site?**  
Anonymous click stream information is collected from every visitor to this site.  This includes pages viewed, date and time, and browser type.  IP numbers are used to determine domain type and in some cases, geographic region.

**How is it used?**  
The information is used by Thirsty Swagman to build anonymous behavioural profiles.  These profiles are used to ensure that our site content is relevant and appropriate for the majority of users.  There is no association to the user’s identity.

**Links**  
This site may contain links to other Web sites.  Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site.  We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**E-mail links**  
We use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail.  We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments.

**Legal disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information if required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the law or comply with any legal process served on Thirsty Swagman.

**Sensitive Information**  
We only collect sensitive information about you with consent.  Sensitive information is information about race, ethnic origin, political views, religion, philosophy, sexual preferences, criminal record or health information.

**Identifiers**  
We do not use identifiers assigned by an external agency or contracted service provider to identify any of our travellers.

**Privacy legislation**  
Thirsty Swagman welcomes the Privacy Amendments (Private Sector) Act 2000 (& the subsequent amendments to this Act) and the 10 privacy Principles that the Act introduces.

If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail [info@thirstyswagman.com](mailto:info@thirstyswagman.com)
